2011年秋天 高科技已经让
By the fall of 2011, technology had taken
人们的生活失去了秘密
a lot of the intrigue out of life.
网络上有每个人的信息墙
The Internet had everyone's wall of information.
任何事都不再神秘了
Nothing was a mystery anymore.
不过 孩子们 在那之前有一段时间
But, kids, there was a time before that,
回到那段黑暗时期
way back in the dark ages.
你们疯了吗
Are you people insane?!
美国最受欢迎的食物是芝士汉堡
The most popular food in America is the cheeseburger!
不可能 是披萨才对
No way! It's pizza!
我们是不是忘了某位香肠先生
Are we forgetting about a certain Mr. Furter,
他的名字叫法兰克福
first name Frank?
嗯 每个孩子午餐盒里带的是什么
Um, what did every kid bring in their lunchbox
直到八年级前的每一天都带
every day till grade eight?
蘸着枫糖浆的薄煎饼
Pancakes with maple syrup.
谢谢你 加拿大
Thanks, Canada.
我们在寻找一种普通美国人吃的食物
We're looking for a food the average American eats.
-没错 没错 -哦
- Yeah. Yeah. - Oh!
中国菜
Chinese food.
后来智能手机出现了
And then came the smartphone.
嘿 还记得
Hey, remember
有一次我们争论什么才是最受欢迎的食物吗
when we were arguing about the most popular food?
是面包
It's bread.
嗯
Hm.
酒吧争论就从此消失了
And the barroom debate was dead.
你们都是白痴
You guys are idiots!
-好吧 没有彻底消失 -你真的要告诉我
- Okay, not completely dead. - You are seriously telling me
你不打算拆开这个信封吧
you don't want to open that envelope
看看你怀的是男孩还是女孩
and find out if you're having a boy or a girl?
不打算 索尼娅医生给我们这个只是为了以防万一我们想知道
Nope. Dr. Sonya only gave us this in case we wanted to know.
但我们不想
But we don't.
莉莉派和我只是想等着宝宝生出来
Lilypad and I are just gonna wait till that baby pops out
然后享受这个巨大的惊喜
and enjoy the big surprise.
听着 我假装持照医生的时间
Look, I have pretended to be a licensed therapist
已经长到能发现你们不想知道孩子性别这件事
enough times to know there is something unhealthy
是很不健康的
about your not wanting to find out.
-支持我一下 凯文 -不 不 不 不 不
- Back me up here, Kev. - No, no, no, no, no.
这名真正的医生不会冒着让
This real therapist won't risk upsetting
他的完美的新女朋友生气的风险去分析她的完美的朋友
his wonderful new girlfriend by analyzing her wonderful friends.
不管他们的精神有多不正常
No matter how mentally unbalanced they may be.
我懂的
I hear you.
我觉得你不懂
I don't think you do.
我们只是不想让那种大男子主义的期望
We just don't want to burden our little angel
给我们的小天使太多的负担
with all kinds of gender-specific expectations.
男孩可以跳芭蕾 女孩也可以打橄榄球
Boys can do ballet; girls can play football.
太对了 绿湾包装工队几年前
Hell, the Green Bay Packers have been
就已经证明了这点了
proving that for years.
要是在体育酒吧的话这个笑话会让人哄堂大笑的
That would've gotten a big laugh at a sports bar.
嗯 我说要早点确定性别
Well, I say define gender roles early.
其它女孩14岁生日得到的都是
All the other girls got a pretty dress
漂亮的裙子和蛋糕
and a cake when they turned 14.
可我
Me...
我想回家 爸爸
I want to go home, Daddy!
那个方向只有狼
That direction is nothing but wolves.
而那边40公里处是斯密舍矿山镇
And 40 kilometers that way is the mining town of Smithers.
要是我就选狼
I'd take my chances with the wolves.
三天后见
I'll see you in three days.
等一下 我吃什么啊
Well, wait, wh-what am I supposed to eat?
嘿 你有把刀 森林里到处是动物
Hey, you've got a knife, the forest is full of animals--
你还想要什么 自助餐吗
what do you want, a buffet?
爸爸
Papa...!
生日快乐 儿子
Happy birthday, son...!
对此有什么想法吗 大夫
Got any thoughts on that, Doc?
如果你们觉得我会有想法的话 那么 你们疯了
If you guys think I'm going near that, you're crazy.
你为什么要强调"你们"
Why'd you emphasize "you're"?
没有原因 你漂亮极了
No reason. You're pretty.
HIMYM字幕组倾情奉献
翻译 园丁姐姐 47.4 ANNIE 安达小充
校对 加菲猪  园丁姐姐 霜之哀伤
顺便问一句 你们明晚想来我们那吗
By the way, do you guys want to come over tomorrow night
我们会准备鸡尾酒和小吃
for sangria and tapas?
听上去好极了
That sounds awesome.
太好了 我们要粉刷育儿室
Great. We're also gonna paint the nursery.
哦 快速更新下 关于鸡尾酒和小吃的那部分
Oh, and a quick update on the sangria and tapas--
取消了 嗯
that's cancelled. Mmm...
猜猜哪个狡猾的混蛋
Guess what smooth son of a bitch
刚刚在吧台泡到妞了
just picked up a girl at the bar?
巴尼 你这么快就已经背着诺拉偷情了吗
Barney, you're cheating on Nora already?
不是 伙计们 是我
No, guys, it's me.
珍妮特·麦肯泰尔
Janet McIntyre.
我在吧台点东西的时候
Struck up a conversation at the bar
和她开聊的 她马上猜到我要点面包
while ordering, she guessed bread right away,
我们笑了 这就是火花 砰 明天
we laughed, it was a thing, boom, going
晚上约会
out tomorrow night.
-然后呢 她就这么答应了 -就这么答应了
- So, she said yes just like that? - Just like that.
她有毛病
There's something wrong with her.
不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no.
停 他们总这么干
Stop it. They always do this.
每次我和一个新认识的女孩约会
Every time I go on a first date
他们都会突然进入调查模式
they snap right into research mode.
它的开始是因为一个意外
It started by accident.
哦
Ooh.
你好
Hello?
泰德 我们上网查了一下
Ted, we did a little Internet research
你的米娅·普拉姆雷
on your Mia Plumley.
我们刚刚给你发了
We just sent you
她六个月前的照片
a picture of her from six months ago.
我不明白 米娅是站在
I don't understand-- is Mia standing behind
那个病态的胖子后 哦 我的天啊
this morbidly obese wo... Oh, my God!
他们有饼干和奶油
They had cookies and cream.
你说的关于女人被迫节食时的感受的那些话
And what you were saying about how women feel
实在是太有道理了
they have to starve themselves makes so much sense.
噢，有热狗。追
Ooh, hot dogs. Score!
从那以后，背景调查
After that, background checks
成为了固定流程
became standard operating procedure.
和娜丁的约会还不错
The date with Nadine went great.
不过你们似乎找到了反对的理由
Unless you guys found something.
坐下来说
Are you sitting down?
不
No.
她因为在弗罗里达吸毒被通缉了
She's wanted in Florida on crystal meth charges.
她驯养血腥斗牛
She breeds pit bulls for dog fighting.
（dog fighting是指让动物相斗以提供消遣，类似角斗士，十分血腥）
-还有，联邦调查局
-这个链接是什么
- Also, the FBI...
- What's this link?
哦，她还在网上写影评
Oh, she also writes online movie reviews.
而且，她现在还是一个死囚的妻子
Anyway, she's still married to a death row inmate convicted...
她只给了《安妮·霍尔》两星
She gave Annie Hall two out of ten stars?
（《安妮·霍尔》是1977年的奥斯卡电影）
拖沓而且被高估
"Slow and overrated"?
不是吧，你就注意到了这个
Really? That's your takeaway?
这可是伍迪·艾伦的巅峰之作
It's the Wood Man at the height of his powers.
他打破第四道墙直接对镜头讲话的方式
The way he broke the fourth wall by talking directly to camera?
从那时候人们就为他痴狂
People have been ripping that off ever since.
他不是吧
Can you believe this guy?
波拉·文森索
Paula Vincenzo.
她在厕所
She's in the bathroom.
她怎么了
What's wrong with her?
疯子一个 她的脸谱网上
Total psycho. Her Facebook wall
有一个与非生物约会的网站链接
has a link to a site about dating inanimate objects.
去年的大部分时间，她都和一个…
For most of last year, she was engaged...
迷你冰箱处在订婚状态 这里有照片
to a mini fridge. And there's pictures:
她和那个迷你冰箱的徒步旅行
her and the mini fridge on a hike,
她和那个迷你冰箱在葡萄园
her and the mini fridge in wine country,
这是那个迷你冰箱在会见岳父母……
here's the mini fridge meeting her parents...
快闪人
Run like the wind.
翻译 园丁姐姐 47.4 ANNIE 安达小充
校对 加菲猪  园丁姐姐 霜之哀伤
呃……想到我那儿去吗
So... want to go back to my place?
嗯，好吧
Yeah, all right.
托我们的福，你尖叫着
Well, thanks to us, you ran screaming from
从那个变态那里逃走了，对吧
that freak show, right?
-完全正确
-整个一疯子啊
- Absolutely.
- Cuckoo!
所以说嘛
So what's the problem?
你需要我们
You need us.
不，我不需要，好吧
No, I don't, okay?
我不想要背景调查
I don't want a background check.
我想要冒险和刺激
I want adventure and excitement.
听着，如果我要在
Look, if it's a choice
谜题和历史之间选择
between mystery and history,
我选择谜题
I want mystery.
事实上……
In fact...
泰德，我觉得……
Ted, I wouldn't...
啊，珍妮特
Uh, Janet.
我有一个想法 人们不再拥有
I have a theory. People don't get the chance
了解对方的机会，所以……
to just discover each other anymore, so...
我有个提议
here's my idea.
在我们明天的约会之间
Before we go out tomorrow,
请不要上网搜对方的信息
let's not do any prior Internet research on each other.
我听起来是不是在隐瞒什么不良信息
It sounds like I'm hiding something horrible, doesn't it?
我百分之百确定你是个连环杀手
I'm pretty sure you're a serial killer.
我不是 我不是
I'm not. I'm not.
我的意思是，你看，我爸妈认识的时候
It's just, you know, like, when my parents met,
还没有互联网——他们只是
they didn't have the Internet--they just went out
约了个会就相爱了
on a blind date and fell in love.
很好啊 他们还在一起吗
That's nice. And they're still together?
直到他们离婚的时候都在一起
Right up to the divorce.
我的意思是，我很想了解你本人
The point is, I'd love to get to know you
而不是网络信息
in person, not on my computer.
想法不错 开始听起来
I like that. What started out
很诡异 事实上还挺有爱的
sounding really creepy turned out really sweet.
这是我的行事风格
That's kind of my move.
她居然
And she was
同意了“无网约会”
on board with the whole "no Internet" thing?
她觉得很有爱
She loved it.
这个女人有不可告人的秘密
The bitch is hiding something.
这个女人肯定有不可告人的秘密
The bitch is totally hiding something.
嘿 泰德 你走之前问一句—
Hey, Ted, before you leave--
是珍妮特·麦-艾-金太尔还是麦金太尔
is Janet McIntyre M-A-C or M-C?
最后说一次，在和她约会之前
For the last time, I don't want to know
我不想知道她的任何信息
anything about her before the date.
你可能想看看这个 泰德 有裸照
You might want to see this, Ted-- naked pictures.
那不是珍妮特
That's not Janet.
那是谁
Who, now?
说正经的
Seriously...
如果你们尊重我这个朋友
if you guys respect me as a friend...
就别查了
stop looking.
呃 既然泰德的意思很清楚了 那么
Well, Ted was pretty clear there, so...
我们就关掉本本
let's shut those laptops
去帮马修和莉莉 我们说好的
and go help Lily and Marshall, just like we promised.
把本本留在这里 去粉刷婴儿室
Let's leave the laptops here and go paint that baby room.
别带本本
Without laptops.
带就带吧 无所谓
Or bring the laptops. Either way.
激动人心的时刻
This is exciting.
给你们看看
I give you...
伴随我们宝宝长大的颜色
the color our child will grow up with.
黄色，像太阳一样
Yellow, like the sun.
也可能是女儿 近音双关
Or daughter. Pun snuggle.
（sun-太阳与son-儿子发音相近）
哦，天哪，宝宝马上就要入住了
Oh, God, this room's about to get its first spit-up.
打开信封不就完事了
Just open the envelope already!
凯文，你能不能告诉巴尼
Kevin, will you please tell Barney that it is
想保持神秘感是很正常的？
perfectly normal for us to want to preserve the mystery.
我不是来做分析的 我是来给自己加男友分的
I'm not here to analyze; I'm here to win boyfriend points.
顺便说一句，你们都很靓，尤其是罗宾
By the way, you all look great, especially Robin.
好吧，如果你们不知道孩子的性别
Come on, if you don't know the gender,
在婴儿洗礼上会被鄙视的
you're gonna get generic crap at the baby shower.
（婴儿洗礼是孩子出生前举办的一个party）
但如果你们真的知道了性别
But if you do know the gender,
你们就会
you'll get, oh,I don't know, this!
马修 关灯
Marshall! Lights!
好吧
Okay.
当这个小男孩儿还不能双飞的时候
BARNEY: When little Jack's not turning double plays,
他会穿着这身
he's turning heads with this
家庭版本垒打的帅气衣服
home run of an outfit!
但如果是一个小女孩儿
And if it's a little girl...
这身皇家公主一样的打扮会让你无话可说的
This royal ensemble may leave you speechless,
而我们的小公主一定会说
but it's sure to make little Sally say,
我奈你妈妈我奈我的衣服
"I wuv you, Mommy, and I wuv my dress,
我会很乐意看到你洗澡的样子的
and I would love to see you in the shower."
不好意思我太投入这个角色了
Sorry, I kind of fell out of character in that last part.
但如果你们不知道它的性别
But if you don't know the gender...
我们的小朋友就只能像一个在操场上被遗弃的小孩子一样
Little Fran is sure to be the pariah of the playground
穿着这身像雌雄同体一样的麻布衣了
in this hermaphroditic burlap sack.
马修 开灯
Marshall! Lights!
巴尼
Barney,
你一点也不在乎我们孩子的性别
you don't really care abo'.
你只是不能
No. You just
忍受
can't stand
你不知道的一些事情
not knowing something.
这太荒唐了
That's ridiculous!
马修你能
Marshall, will you...
帮我拿着这些东西一小会儿么
will you hold these for a second?
当然你要干什么
Yeah, sure. Why?
我一定要知道
Because I gots to know!
哦 巴尼 帮我把他推开
Oh, Barney, no!Help! Get him off of me!
所有人都hold住
Everybody hold it Hold it!
我发现珍妮特·麦肯泰尔当过三次寡妇
I found Janet McIntyre,who's been widowed three times.
很显然她杀了他的老公们
She's obviously killing her husbands!
我勒个去
Oh, my God!
他们约会已经六分钟了
They're six minutes into the date.
泰德可能已经对她说我爱你了
Ted's probably already told her that he loves her!
我们必须赶到那儿去
We've got to get down there!
没人要离开
Nobody's going anywhere!
为什么
Why?!
孩子们 就在那会儿
NARRATOR:Kids, at that moment,
凯文想起了之前他定下的规矩
Kevin thought backto his earlier rule...
我这个真正的心理医生
This real therapist won't risk
不会去冒着惹火他完美的女朋友的风险
upsetting his wonderful new girlfriend
去分析她这些完美的朋友们
by analyzing her wonderful friends.
凯文把这些规矩统统抛弃了
...and threw it out the window.
你们是我见过的最最相互依赖的乱七八糟的
You're all the most codependent, incestuous,
喜欢控制别人的一群人了
controlling group of people I've ever met!
顺便说一句 你们都很不错 尤其是罗宾
By the way, you all look great, especially Robin.
哦 别
Oh, mm-mm.
这真的很棒
This is so great.
对吧 如果我们事先调查了对方
Right? See, if we'd researched each other,
我们都会偷偷的用对话引向
we'd both be secretly steering the conversation
一个方向或另一个方向
one way or the other.
但像我们这样却更刺激不是么
But this is more exciting, right?
老刺激了
Way more exciting.
这样我们就可以谈论任何我们想说的话题了
I mean, we can talk about anything we want.
任何话题
Anything.
所以
So...
来的路上路况怎么样啊
...how was the traffic getting here?
你把我从公寓接来的
You picked me up at my apartment.
我确实这样做了
I certainly did.
老天啊
Oh, my God,
没有了网络我就失去了和女人交流的能力了
I've lost the ability to talk to girls without the Internet.
我的大脑彻底短路了
My brain is completely shutting down.
请问两位是准备吃饭还是只喝东西
So, are you folks gonna have dinner or just drinks?
我不知道
I-I don't know.
你说的到底是什么鬼东西 凯文
What the hell was that, Kevin?
我们都是一群疯子仅仅因为
We're all crazy just because
我上网找了些东西
I'm looking up some stuff on the Internet,
而巴尼希望知道那个孩子的性别么
and Barney wants to know the baby's gender?
这个 老实说
Well,to be honest,
我注意到了另外一些让人不安的东西
I noticed some other disturbing...
算了
Never mind.
当我没说 对不起
It's nothing. I'm sorry.
我必须知道
I gots to know!
好吧 昨天晚上
Okay, last night alone...
你什么时候回来
When-When are you coming back?
因为我想你了小傻瓜
Because I miss you, silly!
等下 你在和谁说话
Wait, who's he talking to?
嘘 我马上就回来
Shh, I'll be back soon.
嗯 你想让我帮你带份椒盐脆饼么
Yeah, you want me to bring you a pretzel?
分离焦虑症
separation anxiety
泰德在洗手间给我发短信
Ted's texting me from the bathroom.
哦
Oh.
我表示我不明真相啊
I don't get it.
-只是发了一个带撇的C啊他 - 哦
- It's just a "C" with an apostrophe.- Oh.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
当有的时候我们中的一个在大号
Sometimes when one of us is on the can,
我们会偷偷看一眼然后发信息给别人
we'll, uh, sneak a peek and then text each other,
你懂的
you know.
用符号来描绘你拉的一坨的样子
Symbols to describe what your bowel movement looks like?
今天早上我拉了一坨像 & 的东西
This morning,I took an ampersand.
去年夏天我拉的像两点
Last summer,I dropped a deuce
看上去确实就像我三点里的两点
that actually looked like the number two!
不合时宜的社会行为举止
inapporopriate social behavior
你上个礼拜三加班的时候
When you worked late Wednesday,
我感到很寂寞
I... I got lonely and...
所以我就一个人偷偷看了幸存者
I watched Survivor without you.
幸存者的内疚感
Survivor guilt
我唯一没能看到的你们不健康的行为
Practically the only unhealthy behavior I didn't see
就是肢体暴力
from you people was physical violence.
耶
Yeah.
至少 我们最近没那样做
At least we don't do that.
其中最极端的就是
And to top it off,
你们只关注干涉泰德的恋爱
all the meddling in Ted's love life,
却不关注莉莉怀孕
not to mention Lily's pregnancy?
这些让我感觉自己被你们刺激的都有点身体功能失调了
It all strikes me as just deeply dysfunctional.
所以综上所述 我们都很正常是么
So what you're saying is,we're fine?
否认
denial
虽然这些字体经常
So, while this font is often
错误的被认为是黑体
mistaken for Helvetica,
事实上
the fact is...
这些是黑粗体
it's Helvetica Bold.
我都能确切的听到
I can actually hear the sound
她的阴道关上门的声音
of her vagina being boarded up.
我必须坦诚珍妮特
I got to be honest, Janet.
首先这是新罗马字体
First of all..this is Times New Roman.
第二 我很纠结
Second, I'm having trouble
怎么能挑出话题
coming up with things to talk about.
我也一直坐在这里想
You? I'm sitting here thinking,
擦 我真希望我能找出一个关于字体的话题
"Damn it, I wish I had something as good as that font thing.
那真是个不错的话题
That's gold."
伙计们 我很抱歉说了那些
Guys, I'm so sorry I said anything.
你基本上把我的朋友们当成了精神病
Um, you basically called my friends mentally ill.
而你却还想仅仅用一点沉闷的道歉化解么
Yeah, you think some lame apology will fix that?
那我一个人粉刷这个屋子怎么样
What if I just paint the rest of the room by myself?
接受你的道歉
ROBIN, LILY & MARSHALL:Apology accepted.
好的那我们这样吧
Okay, let's do this.
我们来找找相互之间的相同和不同
Let-Let's find out each other's likes and dislikes.
就随机找个东西开头吧
Start with something totally random.
比如我不知道怎么说
Like, um, oh, I don't know.
你是我不知道
Are you a fan of--I don't know--
安妮霍尔的粉丝么
Annie Hall?
我想这绝对不是随便的话题你想用这部电影
I'm guessing that's not random at all, and you use that movie
来测试我是不是一个很酷的女孩儿
to test whether a girl is cool?
不不不 这只是一部第一时间跃入我脑海的电影
No, it's-it's the first movie that popped into...
-我喜欢安妮 霍尔  -哦 感谢上帝 你很酷
-I love Annie Hall.  -Oh, thank God you're cool.
但就像一切刚开始那样
But just as things started
和珍妮特·麦肯泰尔相处的开始
to go well with Janet McIntyre...
哇哦 我找到了关于珍妮特·麦肯泰尔的东西
Whoa. I just found Janet McIntyre.
是传说中的珍妮特·麦肯泰尔
The Janet McIntyre.
我 勒 个 去
Sweet... mother... of God!
我要去下洗手间了
Uh, well, I got to run to the restroom.
别上网啊 亲
No internet, Mister.
如果你发现我那些阴暗的秘密我会宰了你的
If you find out my deep, dark secret, I'll have to kill you.
这只是我的朋友在问我约会怎么样
It's just my friends checking up on me.
我会很礼貌的告诉他们我享受了一段美好的时光
I'll politely let them know we're having a lovely time.
好的
Okay.
泰德说 他不会点击链接的让我们让他独处一会儿
Ted says, "I'm not clicking on the link, so leave me alone."
然后又给我发了一堆表示脏话的符号
And then either texted me a bunch of symbols for profanity,
或者是表示拉肚子的符号
or got food poisoning
然后用一直以来最诡异的两点来结尾
and dropped the weirdest deuce of all time.
你们真的应该看看这些
You guys have to see this.
不 我们现在和泰德站在一边
No. We're with Ted on this.
我们不想知道珍妮特是什么人
We don't want to find out about Janet,
就好像我们不想知道孩子的性别一样
just like we don't want to find out about the baby.
因为我们喜欢神秘
Because we like mystery,
不管是威严而毛茸茸的野人
whether it's the hairy majesty of Bigfoot,
还是卓柏卡布拉凶猛的吸血鬼
or the bloodsucking ferocity of the Chupacabra,
还是莉莉肚子里这个奇迹一般的生命的性别
or the gender of our little miracle.
谢谢你啊
Thanks for putting those together
把这些归为一类
in the same sentence, sweetie.
额
Mm.
这样吧如果你们不想知道那这样
Look, if you guys don't want to know, how about this?
让我看看我不会告诉你们的
Let me look,and I won't tell you.
-绝对不行  -可以
-Absolutely not.  -Fine.
亲爱的 如果我们不让他歇会儿
Baby, if it will shut him up,
谁知道他会做出什么
what's the harm?
我可以么
Can I...?
我感觉我犯了个错误
This may have been a mistake.
男孩儿
Boy!
我喜欢孩子吗
Do I like babies!
女
Girl!
朋友
...friend,
你的头发看上去真不错
your hair looks fantastic!
双胞胎
Twins!
是1988年的一部超好的电影
was the feel-good movie of 1988.
好了 巴尼我们不会在乎你说什么的
Okay, Barney, hey, it doesn't matter what you guys say.
我们不会感兴趣的
We're not gonna cave.
不 我们想知道
Yes, we are!
哦 睁开眼睛看看
Oh, just open your eyes.
这种中性的黄色看上去糟透了
This gender-neutral yellow is horrible!
我们肯定要重新粉刷的
We're clearly gonna paint over the whole thing!
这就是你想听的
That's what you want to hear.
老娘我一定要知道
I gots to know!
耶
Yeah.
是一个
"It's a..."
是个
It's a...
剩下的卡片去哪里了
Where is the rest of the card?
我把它撕成两半了
I ripped it in half.
我知道你极其渴望看一看
I knew you'd be desperate to see it,
当然我会把它给你的
and I'll give it to you.
你只需要读一读珍妮特·麦肯泰尔的事情
All you have to do is admit that mystery is stupid
然后承认神秘感是愚蠢的
by reading about Janet McIntyre.
这一点都是不是感情勒索
This is in no way emotional extortion.
你们要不要这么赞
You guys are great.
好吧 让我们来看看你本本
Fine, we'll look at your laptop.
我
Sweet...
勒 个 去
mother... of God.
我没看到电脑屏幕
I can't really see the computer screen.
只是被呛到了
It just went down the wrong pipe.
[莉莉和我都坚决认为你得看看这个关于珍妮特·麦肯泰尔的链接]
哇
Whoa.
要是莉莉和马修要我看看
If Lily and Marshall want me to click on it,
那估计珍妮特·麦肯泰尔真是有什么不为人知的阴暗面了
maybe Janet really does have a deep, dark secret.
肿么了
What's going on?
我是个妓女
I'm a prostitute.
你该不会以为我
You didn't think I was
真的是看上你了吧
actually into you, did you?
有点
Sort of.
淡定点 莫斯比
Get it together, Mosby.
噢
Oh.
这酒喝了又得还回去哈
You don't buy beer,you rent it.
对吧
Am I right?
这可是男厕所
This is the men's room.
我知道
I know.
我是男人啊
I'm a dude.
听着，有些事情你应该知道
Listen, there's something you should know.
我撒谎了
I lied.
我只对安妮·霍尔这电影只有一点点喜欢
I only kind of liked Annie Hall.
我得看看
I gots to know!
我
Sweet...
勒 个 去
mother... of God.
嘿
Hey.
泰德 你还好吧 你看起来有点被吓到了
Ted, are you okay? You look freaked out.
我哪有
I'm not freaked out.
我很被吓到了 为啥呢
I was freaked out. Why?
因为我刚发现了珍妮特·麦肯泰尔
'Cause I had just discovered that Janet McIntyre was...
超级赞
amazing!
珍妮特·麦肯泰尔:15岁的普林斯顿大学毕业生
Janet McIntyre:Princeton Grad at Age Fifteen
普林斯顿神童珍妮特·麦肯泰尔向陌生人捐肾
Princeton prodigy Janet McIntyre donates kidney to complete stranger
肾脏捐献者登上珠穆朗玛峰
Kidney donor climbs Everest
最年轻的珠穆朗玛峰登峰者从河里救了一个孩子
Youngest woman to climb everest saves baby from creek
挽救了孩子的天才少女继承了麦肯泰尔家族的亿万财富
Baby-saving Genius inherits billion dollar McIntyre Fortune
我想找个人一起抱着看安妮·霍尔
I just want someone to cuddle up with & watch Annie Hall
然后 那堵信息墙出现了
And just like that, the wall went up.
好吧 他看到了珍妮特·麦肯泰尔的
Okay, he looked at Janet McIntyre's
网上超强事迹
Internet extravaganza.
这是卡片的另一半
Here's the other half of the card.
等等 我们应该这样做吗
Wait. Should we do this? I...
我不知道 我的意思是 我内心深处有个声音说 不应该
I don't know. I mean, my soul says no,
但是这些丑陋的黄色墙却尖叫着说 应该
but these hideous yellow walls scream yes.
那我是停下来 还是
Should I just stop, or...?
我勒个去
Sweet mother of God!
一只狗从渥太华跑到了萨斯卡通
A dog in Ottawa ran all the way to Saskatoon!
怎么
What?
我们已经把珍妮特·麦肯泰尔人肉了个底朝天了
We figured out the Janet thing.
我得看看加拿大的新闻啊
I'm catching up on Canada.
你是赞同我这样做的吧？
You're with me on this, right?
不然的话 我得下去把纸条捡回来
Otherwise, I can go down,and I can get the card.
绝对赞同
Absolutely.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
所以 孩子的性别依然是一个迷
And so the gender remained a secret,
但是 珍妮特·麦肯泰尔的生活却不再是了
but Janet McIntyre's life no longer was.
只有一个问题
There was only one problem.
泰德 怎么了
Ted, what's going on?
没事
Nothing.
我有没有跟你说过我是纽约建筑史上
Did I mention that I'm the youngest architect
最年轻的摩天大楼的建筑师
in New York historyto have a skyscraper built?
噢 所以 我也没有你想像的那么
Oh.So, I'm not quite
的默默无闻啦
as far beneath you as you might think.
为什么我要那样想
Why would I think that?
没啥原因 但是我六年级时
No reason, but this one time in sixth grade,
我见到一只浣熊被困在了排水沟里 然后我告诉我爸爸
I saw a raccoon trapped in a gutter, and I told my dad,
后来 消防员们来把它救出来了
and the firemen came and got it out,
虽然这不像我把孩子从河里救出来或别的事那么伟大
so it's not like I pulled a baby from a creek or anything,
至少 我没有因事小而不为之
but at least I didn't ignore it
而且我还用放大镜把萤火虫烧着了
and keep lighting bugs on fire with my magnifying glass.
我们有过约定的 但是你打破了
We had one promise, and you broke it.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
你查了我 结果现在你发现我很可怕了
You looked me up, and now you find me intimidating.
为什么我要觉得你很可怕呢
Why-Why would I find you intimidating, okay?
这又不像我捐了个肾
It's not like I donated a kidney,
但我曾经献过血
but I donated blood once,
尽管我紧张得昏过去了
although I wound up fainting,
然后他们不得不把血又输回去了
and they had to put it all back in.
这些事真是让我超激动
I was so excited about this.
但现在你和其他人一样就像个又哭又闹的蠢蛋
But now you're just a blubbering idiot like the rest of them.
我不是
No, I ain't!
我是说 我哪里又哭又闹了
I mean, no, I never do that thing you says.
我的意思是 你比我优秀太多
What I mean is, you gooder than me
是没什么关系的
no make difference!
就那样了
And that's that.
我真希望我没去点那个网页
I wish to God I'd never clicked on that link.
真是遗憾 泰德
I'm sorry, Ted.
我们只是想帮帮忙
We were just trying to help.
我觉得的那是咸吃萝卜淡操心
I said it was meddling and manipulative,
但是凯文非要我们插手
but Kevin insisted we butt in.
病态的惯性骗子
pathological liar
不 是我的错
No, it's my fault.
我不应该看的
I never should have looked.
在这场神秘VS史实大对抗中
In the battle of mystery versus history,
还是不要知道的比较好
it's best not to know.
莉莉
Lily Pad
怎么
What?
我们有个男宝宝了
We're having a boy.
我们有个男宝宝啦
我们有个男宝宝啦 你有个男宝宝了
We're having a boy! You're having a boy!
我们有个男宝宝了
We're having a boy.
我去买些蓝色的画
I'll go buy some blue paint.
刀得磨一磨了
It needs sharpening.
你看到了吧  我三天前就说 你会很快回来的
You see? I told you three days would go by in no time.
菲利斯 起飞吧
Phineas, take us up!
要是你想问我
Well, in case you were wondering,
我在加勒比海的时候是不是一直在下雨
it rained the entire time I was in the Caribbean.
那么 谢谢你的关心
Thank you for asking.
翻译 园丁姐姐 47.4 ANNIE 安达小充
校对 加菲猪  园丁姐姐 霜之哀伤